Guide to the Lewis Perry Curtis Family Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- L. P. Curtis Professional, 1912-1976; Series I; 5.4 linear feet (13 boxes)
  - Correspondence
    - Furniss, Warren Todd(*), 1942-1965, undated (Box 4, Folder 114-15)
    - G, 1915-1971, undated (Box 4, Folder 116)
    - Gambrell, Carroll B., 1944-1952 (Box 4, Folder 117)
    - Gardiner, Emily, 1933-1971, undated (Box 4, Folder 118)
    - Garrett, Roy, Jr., 1944-1945 (Box 4, Folder 119)
    - Gaze, Harold(*), 1924-1928 (Box 4, Folder 120)
    - Ginsberg, Stephen F., 1941-1945 (Box 4, Folder 121)
    - Given, Davis(*), 1939-1967, undated (Box 4, Folder 122-126)
    - Given, Dorothy, 1943-1968 (Box 4, Folder 127)
    - Given, William, 1944-1948 (Box 4, Folder 128)
    - Glasgow, Mary C.(*), 1952-1972 (Box 4, Folder 129)
    - Goldman, Sherwin M., 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 130)
    - Goodchild, Donald, 1931-1933 (Box 4, Folder 131)
    - Goodenough, Erwin, 1958, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 132)
    - Goodhart, Arthur, 1944-1955 (Box 4, Folder 133)
    - Griffin, Martin I. J., 1965 (Box 4, Folder 134)
    - Grigg, Sir Percy James, 1952-1961 (Box 4, Folder 135)
    - Griswold, A. Whitney, 1931-1962, undated (Box 4, Folder 136)
    - Ha - He, 1926-1975 (Box 5, Folder 137)
    - Hi - Hy, 1915-1968, undated (Box 5, Folder 138)
    - Hackney H. Hamilton, 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 139)
    - Haight, Gordon Sherman, 1929-1970 (Box 5, Folder 140)
    - Haight, Mary, 1954-1975 (Box 5, Folder 141)
    - Hale, Earl D.(*), 1923-1962 (Box 5, Folder 142)
    - Ham, Roswell Gray, 1932-1945 (Box 5, Folder 143)
    - Hamilton, Harlan W., 1932-1968 (Box 5, Folder 144)
    - Hamilton, Mary A., 1951-1953 (Box 5, Folder 145)
    - Harrison, F. H.(*), 1929-1953 (Box 5, Folder 146)
    - Hartley, Lodewick C., 1943 (Box 5, Folder 147)
    - Henry, E. Huntington Library, 1933 (Box 5, Folder 148)
    - Hewitt, Norman S.(*), 1938-1974 (Box 5, Folder 149)
    - Hewitt, Patrick, 1945, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 150)
    - Hewitt, Peter, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 151)
    - Hewitt, Ruth,(*), 1936-1943 (Box 5, Folder 152)
    - Hilles, Frederick W.(*), 1928-1974 (Box 5, Folder 153-154)
    - Hinmen, Margaret Wade, 1922-1927 (Box 5, Folder 155)
    - Hogan, Caroline C., 1940-1959, undated (Box 5, Folder 156)
    - Hogan, Charles Beecher(*), 1931-1954 (Box 5, Folder 157)
    - Holden, Reuben A., 1968-1974 (Box 5, Folder 158)
    - Hotchkiss, Horace L., 1943 (Box 5, Folder 159)
    - Humphreys, John A., 1941-1950 (Box 5, Folder 160)
    - Hutchinson, Virginia, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 161)
    - Hutchinson, William R., 1954, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 162)
    - Hyde, Mary, 1956-1975 (Box 5, Folder 163)
    - I, 1946-1949 (Box 5, Folder 164)
    - Irving, Robert G., 1965-1972 (Box 5, Folder 165)
    - J, 1928-1969, undated (Box 5, Folder 166)
    - Jackson, Dorothy, 1956-1957 (Box 5, Folder 167)
    - Jackson Rose H., 1956-1964, undated (Box 5, Folder 168)
    - James, Henry, Jr., 1940-1949 (Box 5, Folder 169)
    - Jenkins, John Newell, 1943-1949 (Box 5, Folder 170)
    - Johnson, Dudley, 1939-1940 (Box 5, Folder 171)
    - Judd, Gerrit P. IV(*), 1940-1959, undated (Box 5, Folder 172)
    - K, 1941-1975 (Box 6, Folder 173)
    - Kaufman, Paul, 1959-1965 (Box 6, Folder 174)
    - Kenna, Frank, 1942-1946 (Box 6, Folder 175)
    - Kent, Sherman(*), 1932-1975 (Box 6, Folder 176)
    - Kerr, Chester, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 177)
    - Kidder, Jerome, 1917, 1929 (Box 6, Folder 178)
    - Kirkpatrick, Ralph, 1944-1974 (Box 6, Folder 179)
    - Knapp, Lewis M., 1931-1932 (Box 6, Folder 180)
    - Koch, Dorothy A., 1946-1948 (Box 6, Folder 181)
    - Koslow, David S., 1969-1973, undated (Box 6, Folder 182)
    - Krieger, Leonard, 1940-1941, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 183)
    - Kubie, Lawrence S.(*), 1957-1973 (Box 6, Folder 184)
    - Kutschera, Anna(*), 1924-1930 (Box 6, Folder 185)
    - La - Li, 1926-1974, undated (Box 6, Folder 186)
    - Lo - Ly, 1930-1969 (Box 6, Folder 187)
    - LaFarge, Mabel, 1932-1943 (Box 6, Folder 188)
    - Lam, George L., 1945, 1961-1962 (Box 6, Folder 189)
    - Lansdowne[underline], 1932-1933 (Box 6, Folder 190)
    - Lascelles, Alice, 1966, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 191)
    - Leddy, Andrew J., 1960-1966 (Box 6, Folder 192)
    - Lewis, Wilmarth Sheldon, 1959-1968 (Box 6, Folder 193)
    - Lindsay, Isabella, 1931-1933, undated (Box 6, Folder 194)
    - Lindsay, John V., 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 195)
    - Lohmann, Ann, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 196)
    - Lohmann, Carl A.(*), 1927-1959, undated (Box 6, Folder 197)
    - Lossby, Andrew, 1942-1945 (Box 6, Folder 198)
    - Lovejoy, Amanda, 1926-1933 (Box 6, Folder 199)
    - Lowndes, Marion Smith, 1958-1974 (Box 6, Folder 200)
    - Lucalts, Norah, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 201)
    - Lutkins, Larue R., 1946-1957 (Box 6, Folder 202)
    - Mac, 1933-1974 (Box 7, Folder 203)
    - Mag - Mu, 1924-1971, undated (Box 7, Folder 204)
    - McArthur, Jeanne, 1971-1975 (Box 7, Folder 205)
    - McDill, John Harcourt(*), 1930-1976, undated (Box 7, Folder 206-209)
    - McDill, Julia Lee, 1930-1974 (Box 7, Folder 210)
    - Macdonald of the Isles, Alice, 1931-1933, undated (Box 7, Folder 211)
    - MacKenty, Bunny Walker, 1933-1949 (Box 7, Folder 212)
    - MacLean, Kenneth(*), 1939-1958, undated (Box 7, Folder 213)
    - Mair, George, 1916-1929 (Box 7, Folder 214)
    - Makepeace, LeRoy, 1942-1943 (Box 7, Folder 215)
    - Melhorn, Frank, 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 216)
    - Mendenhall, Thomas C., 1951-1957 (Box 7, Folder 217)
    - Merriman, Daniel(*), 1943-1962 (Box 7, Folder 218)
    - Merriman, Mary(*), 1948-1963, undated (Box 7, Folder 219)
    - Metzdorf, Robert F., 1952-1968 (Box 7, Folder 220)
    - Moe, Henry Allen(*), 1942-1953 (Box 7, Folder 221)
    - Moffly, Charles K., 1958-1960 (Box 7, Folder 222)
    - Mommsen, Theodor, 1944 (Box 7, Folder 223)
    - Monkman, Kenneth, 1966-1975 (Box 7, Folder 224)
    - Morehouse, Harold E., 1929 (Box 7, Folder 225)
    - Murdoch, R. Alan, 1960-1974 (Box 7, Folder 226)
    - Murdock, Harold, 1929 (Box 7, Folder 227)
    - N, 1924-1974, undated (Box 7, Folder 228)
    - Nadel, George H., 1963 (Box 7, Folder 229)
    - Nettleton, George H., 1927-1929 (Box 7, Folder 230)
    - Newton, A. Edward, 1932 (Box 7, Folder 231)
    - Notestein, Ada Comstock, 1943-1954 (Box 7, Folder 232)
    - Notestein, Wallace(*), 1929-1967 (Box 7, Folder 233-235)
    - O, 1929-1970, undated (Box 8, Folder 236)
    - Ollard, Richard, 1966-1969 (Box 8, Folder 237)
    - Ollard, S. L., 1931 (Box 8, Folder 238)
    - Olmsted, Alexander, 1924-1930 (Box 8, Folder 239)
    - Olmsted, Ashley Williams(*), 1938-1941, undated (Box 8, Folder 240)
    - Oppen, Beate R. von(*), 1958-1964, undated (Box 8, Folder 241)
    - Ossorio, Frederic Eric(*), 1940-1972 (Box 8, Folder 242-251)
    - Owen, David(*), 1933-1966, undated (Box 8, Folder 252)
    - Owen, Louise, 1936-1969, undated (Box 8, Folder 253)
    - Owen, William Post, 1959-1961, undated (Box 8, Folder 254)
    - Pa - Pe, 1912-1970, undated (Box 8, Folder 255)
    - Pf - Pu, 1926-1972, undated (Box 8, Folder 256)
    - Palmer, John, 1956-1965, undated (Box 8, Folder 257)
    - Palmer, Holkins, D., 1943-1945 (Box 8, Folder 258)
    - Pargellis, Stanley, 1941-1964 (Box 8, Folder 259)
    - Parr, L. F., 1930-1932 (Box 8, Folder 260)
    - Pascoe, Charles R.(*), 1943-1952, undated (Box 8, Folder 261)
    - Patten, Lewis, 1926-1945 (Box 8, Folder 262)
    - Pearson, Norman Holmes, 1942-1969 (Box 9, Folder 263)
    - Pearson, Rodney(*), 1963-1971 (Box 9, Folder 264)
    - Petrucelli, R. Joseph, 1964-1972 (Box 9, Folder 265)
    - Pfeffer, Robert, 1945-1949 (Box 9, Folder 266)
    - Phelips, Constance(*), 1927-1930 (Box 9, Folder 267)
    - Phillips, Leonard B., 1951-1953 (Box 9, Folder 268)
    - Pierson, George W.(*), 1953-1971 (Box 9, Folder 269)
    - Porter, Quincy, 1957, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 270)
    - Porter, Thomas A., 1956-1960 (Box 9, Folder 271)
    - Pressman, Jeffrey L., 1964-1967 (Box 9, Folder 272)
    - Purdy, Richard Little, 1927-1951 (Box 9, Folder 273)
    - Q, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 274)
    - R, 1923-1968, undated (Box 9, Folder 275)
    - Reed, Nathaniel, 1955-1960 (Box 9, Folder 276)
    - Rhodes, Richard L., 1958-1961 (Box 9, Folder 277)
    - Ritterbush, Philip, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 278)
    - Robinson, Pat, 1916-1918 (Box 9, Folder 279)
    - Rosendale, J. King, 1939-1944 (Box 9, Folder 280)
    - Rosenzweig, Saul, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 281)
    - Rostow, Eugene V., 1931-1968, undated (Box 9, Folder 282)
    - Rubini, Dennis A., 1962-1965 (Box 9, Folder 283)
    - Russell, Mary, 1930 (Box 9, Folder 284)
    - Rutishauser, Helen, 1960-1963 (Box 9, Folder 285)
    - Sa - Sc, 1924-1971, undated (Box 9, Folder 286)
    - Se - Sp, 1915-1973 (Box 9, Folder 287)
    - st - su, 1926-1966, undated (Box 9, Folder 288)
    - Scheibler, Edward H.(*), 1953-1969 (Box 9, Folder 289)
    - Schilling, Bernard N.(*), 1939-1965 (Box 9, Folder 290-291)
    - Schilling, Michael S.(*), 1963-1968 (Box 9, Folder 292)
    - Scully, David W., 1949-1951 (Box 9, Folder 293)
    - Seymour, Charles, 1933-1949 (Box 9, Folder 294)
    - Shepard, Henry B., 1948-1954 (Box 9, Folder 295)
    - Silverman, Oscar A., 1932-1945 (Box 9, Folder 296)
    - Sisam, Kenneth, 1927-1928 (Box 9, Folder 297)
    - Smith, Brenton H., 1947-1948 (Box 9, Folder 298)
    - Smith, Charles G., Jr., 1932, undated (Box 9, Folder 299)
    - Smith, Donald A., 1966-1969 (Box 9, Folder 300)
    - Steenlet, Jacques, 1969, undated (Box 9, Folder 301)
    - Steer, Francis W., 1956-1972 (Box 9, Folder 302)
    - Steuart, A. Francis(*), 1927-1932, undated (Box 9, Folder 303)
    - Stevens, Robert B., 1959-1962 (Box 9, Folder 304)
    - Stricklen, Charles G., Jr., 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 305)
    - Sullivan, Edward D. S., 1952-1962, undated (Box 9, Folder 306)
    - Sussman, George D., 1965-1969 (Box 9, Folder 307)
    - Suter, Eugene F.(*), 1958-1966 (Box 9, Folder 308)
    - T, 1929-1968, undated (Box 10, Folder 309)
    - Taft, Seth Chase, 1943-1945 (Box 10, Folder 310)
    - Tempest, Valerie, 1951-1960 (Box 10, Folder 311)
    - Teter, Park, 1956-1967 (Box 10, Folder 312)
    - Tholsen, Trygve, 1950-1971 (Box 10, Folder 313)
    - Thompson, Daniel Varney, Jr.(*), 1931-1933 (Box 10, Folder 314)
    - Thompson, William C., Jr., 1943-1945 (Box 10, Folder 315)
    - Tilney, John, 1953-1954 (Box 10, Folder 316)
    - Tinker, Chauncey B., 1925-1945 (Box 10, Folder 317)
    - Truslow, Ann(*), 1924-1929 (Box 10, Folder 318-319)
    - Tucci, Nicolo(*), 1939-1940 (Box 10, Folder 320)
    - Tuttle, Day, 1957, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 321)
    - Tyler, Eugenie C.(*), 1943-1972 (Box 10, Folder 322)
    - Tyler, Morris(*), 1931-1974 (Box 10, Folder 323)
    - Tyng, Lila, 1953-1972, undated (Box 10, Folder 324)
    - Upper, John L., 1949, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 325)
    - V, 1927-1954 (Box 10, Folder 326)
    - Vincendt, Stefen de, 1923-1930 (Box 10, Folder 327)
    - Wa - We, 1922-1974, undated (Box 10, Folder 328)
    - Wh - Wr, 1922-1975, undated (Box 10, Folder 329)
    - Wallace, Thomas C., 1961-1968 (Box 10, Folder 330)
    - Waring, Joseph Frederick, 1922-1952 (Box 10, Folder 331-332)
    - Welch, Emily W., 1923-1933, undated (Box 10, Folder 333)
    - White, Nelson Cooke(*), 1918-1971 (Box 10, Folder 334-337)
    - Wickwire, Franklin B., 1959-1964 (Box 11, Folder 338)
    - Wiggin, Lewis Merriam(*), 1948-1962, undated (Box 11, Folder 339)
    - Wilcox, Constance (Princess Pignatelli), 1924 (Box 11, Folder 340)
    - Wilder, Isabel, 1958-1976 (Box 11, Folder 341)
    - Willcox, William, 1956, undated (Box 11, Folder 342)
    - Williams, George W., 1948, 1950, undated (Box 11, Folder 343)
    - Williams, John Stanton(*), 1920-1926 (Box 11, Folder 344)
    - Willis-Bund, Frank L. M., 1959-1975 (Box 11, Folder 345)
    - Wolfenden, James(*), 1950-1966 (Box 11, Folder 346)
    - Woolsey, John M., 1939-1940 (Box 11, Folder 347)
    - Work, James A., 1931-1939 (Box 11, Folder 348)
    - Wotkyns, Margaret P., 1920-1926 (Box 11, Folder 349)
    - Y - Z, 1927-1967 (Box 11, Folder 350)
    - Unidentified: First names A - S, 1929-1975, undated,1933-1969, undated (Box 11, Folder 351-354)
    - Unidentified: First names T - W, 1930-1969, undated (Box 11, Folder 355)
    - Unidentified, 1921-1972, undated (Box 11, Folder 356)
  - Other Papers
    - Examination, schedule, 1942, 1945 (Box 11, Folder 357)
    - Archbishop of York papers
      - Questionnaire, 1764 (Box 11, Folder 358)
      - Answers: Abberford-Bessenby, 1764 (Box 11, Folder 359)
      - Answers: Beswick Chapel-Broughton, 1764 (Box 11, Folder 360)
      - Answers: Bubwith-Crambe, 1764 (Box 11, Folder 361)
      - Answers: Crambe-Faceby Church, 1764 (Box 11, Folder 362)
      - Answers: Fangfoss-Guisley, 1764 (Box 11, Folder 363)
      - Answers: Hackness-Holme on Spaldingmoor, 1764 (Box 12, Folder 364)
      - Answers: Holme upon the Wolds-Illingworth Chapel, 1764 (Box 12, Folder 365)
      - Answers: Ingleby Ancliffe-Iastingham, 1764 (Box 12, Folder 366)
      - Answers: Laughton-le-Morthen-Millington, 1764 (Box 12, Folder 367)
      - Answers: Milton-Raskelfe Chapel, 1764 (Box 12, Folder 368)
      - Answers: Rawden Chapel-Sheffield, 1764 (Box 12, Folder 369)
      - Answers: St.Paul's Chapel in Sheffield-Stillingfleet, 1764 (Box 12, Folder 370)
      - Answers: Stillington-Treeton, 1764 (Box 12, Folder 371)
      - Answers: Tunstill-Wighill, 1764 (Box 12, Folder 372)
      - Answers: Wilberfoss-St.Saviour in York, 1764 (Box 12, Folder 373)
      - Microfilm (Box 12, Folder 374)
      - Photostats: 1-120 (Box 12, Folder 375-377)
      - Photostats: 121-697 (Box 13, Folder 378-392)
- L. P. Curtis Family, 1912-1976; Series II; 1.7 linear feet (4 boxed)
  Series II contains Curtis family correspondence and consists of letters written to Lewis Perry Curtis by relatives, one folder of his own letters, and several folders of other material about members of the Curtis family. Following the correspondence are nine folders of miscellaneous materials, including invitations, war ration books, and four folders of genealogical information.
  All correspondence is arranged alpahbetically by the surname of the correspondent and then chronologically. Unidentified correspondence of relatives follows identified correspondence and is found in Box 17, folder 524. The miscellaneous materials fill the last nine folders in the series. Additional letters from relatives may be found in Series III.
  Family members who wrote ten or more letters to Lewis Perry Curtis are noted by an asterisk (*).
  - Adams, Constance Carden, 1958-1976 (Box 14, Folder 393)
  - Bates, Amy Johnson(*), 1942-1953, undated (Box 14, Folder 394-396)
  - Blake, Minnie Catlin, 1924 (Box 14, Folder 397)
  - Browning, Elizabeth, 1931 (Box 14, Folder 398)
  - Browning, Josephine Wells(*), 1928-1970, undated (Box 14, Folder 399-400)
  - Burnham, Virginia Schroeder, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 401)
  - Carden, Constance Sullivan(*), 1931-1976 (Box 14, Folder 402)
  - Carden, George A., Jr., 1953-1965, undated (Box 14, Folder 403)
  - Carden, George A., (1945-) (Box 14, Folder 404)
  - Carden, Timothy, 1958-1974 (Box 14, Folder 405)
  - Carden, William V., 1959-1976 (Box 14, Folder 406)
  - Curtis, Alice Beardsley(*), 1938-1949 (Box 14, Folder 407-408)
  - Curtis, Alison Willis-Bund(*), 1960-1975, undated (Box 14, Folder 409-410)
  - Curtis, Anne, 1945-1953, undated (Box 14, Folder 411)
  - Curtis, B. Farquhar, 1921 (Box 14, Folder 412)
  - Curtis, Beryl, 1946 (Box 14, Folder 413)
  - Curtis, Bonnie, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 414)
  - Curtis, Douglas Craig, 1930-1975 (Box 14, Folder 415)
  - Curtis, E. L. Wells(*), 1915-1947 (Box 14, Folder 416)
  - Curtis, Edward Wells, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 417)
  - Curtis, Elizabeth MacDonald(*), 1913-1961 (Box 14, Folder 418)
  - Curtis, Elizabeth Steele, 1926 (Box 14, Folder 419)
  - Curtis, Harlow P., 1949-1950 (Box 14, Folder 420)
  - Curtis, Jeanet Sullivan, 1933-1943, undated (Box 14, Folder 421)
  - Curtis, Jeanet Sullivan: bills, recepts, etc., 1930, 1945, undated (Box 14, Folder 422)
  - Curtis, Jeanet Sullivan: identification, undated (Box 14, Folder 423)
  - Curtis, Jeanet Sullivan: papers, 1937-1972, undated (Box 14, Folder 424)
  - Curtis, Lewis Beers, 1929-1938, undated (Box 14, Folder 425)
  - Curtis, Lewis Perry (1900-1976)(*), 1930-1943, undated (Box 14, Folder 426)
  - Curtis, Lewis Perry (1900-1976): birth record, 1945 (Box 14, Folder 427)
  - Curtis, Lewis Perry (1900-1976): identification, 1932, undated (Box 14, Folder 428)
  - Curtis, Lewis Perry (1900-1976): papers, 1914-1965 (Box 14, Folder 429)
  - Curtis, Lewis Perry (1900-1976): sketches, 1917 (Box 14, Folder 430)
  - Curtis, Lewis Perry (1932-), 1941-1975, undated (Box 14, Folder 431)
  - Curtis, Lewis Perry (1932-):The Foote School report cards, 1937-1945 (Box 14, Folder 432)
  - Curtis, Louisa Wells(*), 1914-1941, undated (Box 15, Folder 433-446)
  - Curtis, Louisa Wells: Aetna Life Ins. Co. stock, 1931, 1935 (Box 15, Folder 447)
  - Curtis, Louisa Wells: estate, 1944 (Box 15, Folder 448)
  - Curtis, Louisa Wells: visiting cards (Box 15, Folder 449)
  - Curtis, Michael Charles, 1974, undated (Box 15, Folder 450)
  - Curtis, Michael Ellinwood(*), 1941-1952, undated (Box 15, Folder 451)
  - Curtis, Michael Ellinwood: The Foote School report cards, 1936-1943 (Box 15, Folder 452)
  - Curtis, Sarah, undated (Box 15, Folder 453)
  - Desmond, Alice Curtis, 1939-1975, undated (Box 15, Folder 454)
  - Desmond, Thomas C.(*), 1939-1971 (Box 15, Folder 455)
  - Ellsworth, Abby E., 1931-1944, undated (Box 15, Folder 456)
  - The Foote School, 1941-1945 (Box 15, Folder 457)
  - Friends to Curtis Family, 1913-1944 (Box 15, Folder 458)
  - Godfrey, Jonathan, 1929-1945 (Box 15, Folder 459)
  - Groesbeck, Amy(*), 1942-1959, undated (Box 15, Folder 460)
  - Hardigg, Alice Hendrick(*), 1945-1975, undated (Box 16, Folder 461)
  - Hendrick, Arthur Pomeroy, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 462)
  - Hendrick, Elinor Sullivan, 1932-1974 (Box 16, Folder 463)
  - Hendrick, Jacqueline Ewing, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 464)
  - Hendrick, James Pomeroy(*), 1929-1973 (Box 16, Folder 465-467)
  - Hendrick, Josephine Pomeroy, 1939-1952 (Box 16, Folder 468)
  - Hendrick, Robert E. P., 1944, 1957-1973 (Box 16, Folder 469)
  - Hetzel, Joseph Linn, 1926-1932 (Box 16, Folder 470)
  - Hetzel, Mary Wells, 1923, 1926 (Box 16, Folder 471)
  - Leake, Bertha(*), 1924-1945, undated (Box 16, Folder 472)
  - Leake, Eleanora, 1929 (Box 16, Folder 473)
  - Leake, Henry Sabin, 1928 (Box 16, Folder 473)
  - Leake, Quintard, 1927-1929 (Box 16, Folder 474)
  - Leake, Paul, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 475)
  - Maxwell, Carolyn G., 1958 (Box 16, Folder 476)
  - Miani, Beatrice Dempierre, 1962, 1971, undated (Box 16, Folder 477)
  - Padnos, Michael, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 478)
  - Padnos, Nancy Curtis, 1944-1959, undated (Box 16, Folder 479)
  - Padnos, Nancy Curtis: The Foote School report cards, 1944, 1946 (Box 16, Folder 480)
  - Peck, William, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 481)
  - Peck, William, Jr., 1962 (Box 16, Folder 481)
  - Perry, Charlotte(*), 1926-1972, undated (Box 16, Folder 482-483)
  - Perry, Louisa H., 1927 (Box 16, Folder 484)
  - Perry, Richard, 1927 (Box 16, Folder 485)
  - Preparatory school correspondence(*), 1944, 1946 (Box 16, Folder 486)
  - Roche, Austin W., 1956 (Box 16, Folder 487)
  - Roche, James, 1961-1976 (Box 16, Folder 488)
  - Roche, Louise Curtis(*), 1918-1976, undated (Box 16, Folder 489-495)
  - Ruspoli, Alessandro (Edmondo), 1939-1961 (Box 17, Folder 496)
  - Ruspoli, Eugenio, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 497)
  - Ruspoli, Josephine Curtis, 1933 (Box 17, Folder 498)
  - Ruspoli, Mario (Prince de Poggio Suasa), 1929 (Box 17, Folder 498)
  - Schroeder, Henry A., 1964 (Box 17, Folder 499)
  - Shaw, Albert Judson, 1939 (Box 17, Folder 500)
  - Shaw, Katherine Perry(*), 1921-1952, undated (Box 17, Folder 501-502)
  - Sullivan, Catherine E., 1976 (Box 17, Folder 503)
  - Sullivan, Elizabeth Anne, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 503)
  - Sullivan, Janet Loomis, 1930-1944 (Box 17, Folder 504)
  - Sullivan, Mary Barrett(*), 1950-1976 (Box 17, Folder 505-506)
  - Sullivan, Nancy Alison, 1931-1959 (Box 17, Folder 507)
  - Sullivan, Theodore Loomis, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 508)
  - Sullivan, Walter Seager (1866-1949), 1931-1945 (Box 17, Folder 509)
  - Sullivan, Walter Seager (1918-)(*), 1930-1972, undated (Box 17, Folder 510-511)
  - Talleyrand-Périgord, Elizabeth Curtis, undated (Box 17, Folder 512)
  - Vandercock, Fanny, 1920 (Box 17, Folder 513)
  - Wells, Elizabeth, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 514)
  - Wells, Florence Mixter, 1924-1946 (Box 17, Folder 515)
  - Wells, Frederic Brown, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 516)
  - Wells, Jonathan Godfrey, 1945-1949 (Box 17, Folder 517)
  - Wells, Mary Hughes, 1913-1918 (Box 17, Folder 518)
  - Wells, Mary Pomeroy, 1923-1929 (Box 17, Folder 519)
  - Wells, Nettie, 1947-1949 (Box 17, Folder 520)
  - Wells, Pauline Pomeroy(*), 1912-1967, undated (Box 17, Folder 521-523)
  - Unidentified relatives, 1939-1960, undated (Box 17, Folder 524)
  - Clippings, 1972, undated (Box 17, Folder 525)
  - Invitations, 1927, 1938, undated (Box 17, Folder 526)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 17, Folder 527)
  - Post cards, undated (Box 17, Folder 528)
  - Recipes, undated (Box 17, Folder 529)
  - War ration books, undated (Box 17, Folder 530)
  - Bishop family: genealogy, undated (Box 17, Folder 531)
  - Curtis family: genealogical chart, undated (Box 17, Folder 532)
  - Curtis family: genealogy, undated (Box 17, Folder 533)
  - Jones family: genealogy, undated (Box 17, Folder 534)
- Sullivan Family, 1916-1980; Series III; 3.3 linear feet (8 boxes)
  Series III holds the correspondence of the Sullivan family. It includes letters to Jeanet (Sullivan) Curtis, letters written by her to members of her family, and a small quantity of other papers.
  Correspondence is arranged in alphabetical order by surname of correspondent and then in chronological order. Unidentified correspondence is placed after the letters of identified correspondents in Box 25, folders 776-84. Two folders of miscelleaneous papers are in folders 785-86. Other letters of relatives may be found in Series II and additional letters from friends in Series I. Please check under the name and the letter of the surname in the appropriate series.
  Correspondents writing ten or more letters are identified by an asterisk(*).
  - A, 1924-1978, undated (Box 18, Folder 535)
  - Adams, Constance Carden, 1962-1980 (Box 18, Folder 536)
  - Anderson, Margaret, 1964-1978, undated (Box 18, Folder 537)
  - Angell, Molly, 1924 (Box 18, Folder 538)
  - Armstrong, Barbara, 1976, undated (Box 18, Folder 539)
  - Arruda, Roseline, 1937-1939 (Box 18, Folder 540)
  - Ashton, Leigh, 1951-1954 (Box 18, Folder 541)
  - Auchincloss, Reginald, 1947-1979, undated (Box 18, Folder 542)
  - B, 1922-1979, undated (Box 18, Folder 543)
  - Baskin, Myrna F., 1977-1980 (Box 18, Folder 544)
  - Bates, Amy Johnson, 1937-1945 (Box 18, Folder 545)
  - Bates, Robert Chapman, 1928-1941 undated (Box 18, Folder 546)
  - Bernard, Augusta(*), 1938-1956 (Box 18, Folder 547)
  - Biggs, William R.(*), 1927-1934, undated (Box 18, Folder 548-550)
  - Bordley, James III, 1930-1933, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 551)
  - Bordley, Mrs. James, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 551)
  - Bosanquet, Barbara(*), 1932-1979, undated (Box 18, Folder 552-553)
  - Breckinridge, Marvin, 1932-1933 (Box 18, Folder 554)
  - Bresson, Charlotte Clark de, 1954-1960, undated (Box 18, Folder 555)
  - Brewster, Kingman, 1977, undated (Box 18, Folder 556)
  - Brewster, Mary Louise, 1961, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 556)
  - Brieff, Frank, 1963-1974 (Box 18, Folder 557)
  - Browning, Josephine Wells, 1956, 1972-1979 (Box 18, Folder 558)
  - C, 1929-1978, undated (Box 18, Folder 559)
  - Calhoun, Frank Ellinwood(*), 1920-1974, undated (Box 18, Folder 560)
  - Cameron, Olive, 1948-1959, undated (Box 18, Folder 561)